let question_bank = [
    {
    q_no: 1,
    question: "Which National team won the latest FIFA world cup which was held in 2022 ? ",
    answer: "Argentina",
    options: [
      "Brazil",
      "France",
      "Argentina",
      "Uruguay"
    ]
  },
    {
    q_no: 2,
    question: "What is the maximum number of players that are allowed on the field for each side ? ",
    answer: "11",
    options: [
      "05",
      "11",
      "07",
      "12"
    ]
  },
    {
    q_no: 3,
    question: "Which football stadium is known to be the home of FC Barcelona ?",
    answer: "Camp Nou ",
    options: [
      "Anfield ",
      "Camp Nou ",
      "Old Trafford ",
      "Wembly "
    ]
  },
    {
    q_no: 4,
    question: "Who is the player who's won the most Ballon d'Or awards ?",
    answer: "Lionel Messi ",
    options: [
      "Raheem Sterling ",
      "Erling Haaland ",
      "Christiano Ronaldo ",
      "Lionel Messi "
    ]
  },
    {
    q_no: 5,
    question: "In which country was the 2018 FIFA World Cup held in ?",
    answer: "Russia ",
    options: [
      "Qatar ",
      "Japan ",
      "Russia ",
      "United States of America"
    ]
  },
  {
    q_no: 6,
    question: "Which footballer has the highest transfer fee in history ?",
    answer: "Neymar Jr. ",
    options: [
      "Neymar Jr. ",
      "Lionel Messi ",
      "Kylian Mbappe ",
      "Thiago Silva "
    ]
  },
  {
    q_no: 7,
    question: "In year was the first FIFA World Cup held ?",
    answer: "1930 ",
    options: [
      "1948 ",
      "1986 ",
      "1930 ",
      "2000 "
    ]
  },
  {
    q_no: 8,
    question: "which club has won the most UEFA Champions League titles ? ",
    answer: "Real Madrid ",
    options: [
      "Bayern Munich ",
      "FC Barcelona ",
      "Manchester United  ",
      "Real Madrid "
    ]
  },
  {
    q_no: 9,
    question: "For which club does Kylian Mbappe currently play ?",
    answer: "Paris Saint Germain ",
    options: [
      "Paris Saint Germain ",
      "Liverpool ",
      "Real Madrid ",
      "Manchester City"
    ]
  },
  {
    q_no: 10,
    question: "To which club did Lionel Messi move to after leaving PSG ?",
    answer: "Inter Miami FC ",
    options: [
      "FC Barcelona ",
      "Inter Miami FC ",
      "Al - Hilal ",
      "Inter Milan"
    ]
  },
];
